Hello1 23 Sorry I don't know why it didn't work but reload the phone is going to be fine now
sorry
yeah yeah that happens to me sometimes with the zoom app in the phone like it log out and takes
a while to reconnect no worries but yeah thank you for making the time to chat as you saw in
the title of the meeting running a summit rapid so I before having like proposing any solution or dates for
next summit I wanted to chat with exacting members so I could get a sense of your availability and thoughts
about it so just to give you context we are we want to pencil or lock the dates for the
next global summit but we also want to plan a POD or team summit we are thinking about potentially bringing
engineering team together so yeah that's basically it we want to aim to have two summits this year and four
dates we are thinking on having the team summit around. End of Q2.
Like it would be around May and June and global summit around October, November.
So I also wanted to know your availability.
If you have any plans ahead or dates, you know you won't be able to travel.
It's super important to know. So we can also take that into account.
No, I think it's going to be fine. I just. What about location? Because you know.
And it's visa for some.
Yes.
That's why we want to lock the dates as soon as possible because Evgeny recommended that for engineering summit, Poland
is the best location.
But we still need to working on business as soon as possible for you and I think that for Ernie
as well. So that's the main thing.
Like of course we're gonna take into account the visa situation for deciding location, but it will potentially Europe given
location of most of the engineering team and cost of, you know, like moving everyone to one place, like bringing
them to one place. So yeah, that's into consideration.
If you have any recommendations in terms of locations or timelines, you.
Serbia. Serbia is much easier and it's also Europe.
Okay, I'm gonna put that down. I'm gonna research about it and the cost as well.
Yeah, definitely Turkey. But I think Turkey will be more expensive because of distance.
Yeah. The thing with Turkey is no one needs visa. Like no one. I think that no one.
And I think that only Alexander needs a visa and it's super easy because it's like a permit when he
requested. So Turkey would be like the easiest option to be honest.
So why we don't consider Turkey then? And you said Poland.
I mean Poland was if getting suggestion given team location.
But I'm going to do research as well to have a high level overview of that.
Like for example, if most of the team is already located in Poland, flights are going to be more cheaper.
But yeah, I got it, I got, I got it.
If, if, if accommodation is going to be like similar pricing or not.
So I'm gonna do some comparisons to have a.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. But I think I have concerned about Turkey as like tickets, flight tickets.
But everything else I think is gonna be cheaper. And we definitely don't. We even can't. We already was in.
We're in Istanbul. Istanbul, right. We can pick something else.
Yeah. Like Izmir or.
Yeah, yeah. And it will be cheaper as well, I believe because it's not season.
Yeah. I'm going to do a little bit of research.
Please research Serbia and. Yeah. Okay. Because for.
For Poland, I'm not sure even like it's possible to do it in two months. I have no idea.
Because, you know, we like enemies.
Yeah. But you. You should have more than two months. If we decide that location. It's not.
It's not in luck yet, but we should have more than two months to plan and process.
Okay.
Because we are penciling to do it around June. So from now you have at least five months for that.
Sorry, but you said like end of.
The end of Q2, quarter two, so we'll be May or June. Yeah.
Okay, I got it. I got. I have actually, I have a ticket for Turkey in June.
I need to check and I'll let him know. Can you.
Can you check now or.
No, I can't check now, but I'll check if you in. Damn you.
Okay, give me. I'm gonna follow up with you on that so we can review. Make sure you.
Yeah, I think it's the second. The second part of June.
Yes.
I'm gonna share to you on the zoom shot the spreadsheet where you can mark when you are not available
or traveling.
Yeah.
So I know. Yeah. In Both tabs, either Q2 and Q4.
Yeah. Okay.
Thank you so much.
Sorry, sorry, sorry. If you're talking about May or June, Turkey will be much better because it's.
They see that, you know.
Yeah. It's summer, right? It's like spring. Summer, beginning of summer, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Cool. Yeah. Let's see. The other.
The other potential proposal is to lock it during cycle planning so you can work like engineering team and like
roadmap and planning. So that's another potential option for dates proposal that. It's around mid end of June. So. Yeah.
Okay.
Go ahead. Got it.
Okay. Yeah. So please update the spreadsheet as soon as you can with the days you are traveling.
Yes, either, like in Both blocks, either Q2 and Q4 and. Yeah. Thank you. Sounds good.
Thank you. Have a good day.
You too.